[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "How are you coming to terms with what happened?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "coming", "to", "terms", "with", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "Well, the first half an hour was obviously horrendous because I woke up and -- you know was woken up by my son, looked up at the big house, saw 200-foot flames coming out of it, and knew my daughter, nephews, nieces, my mother, and friends were in the house.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "first", "half", "an", "hour", "was", "obviously", "horrendous", "because", "I", "woke", "up", "and", "--", "you", "know", "was", "woken", "up", "by", "my", "son", ",", "looked", "up", "at", "the", "big", "house", ",", "saw", "200-foot", "flames", "coming", "out", "of", "it", ",", "and", "knew", "my", "daughter", ",", "nephews", ",", "nieces", ",", "my", "mother", ",", "and", "friends", "were", "in", "the", "house", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "Were you surprised how fast this happened?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "surprised", "how", "fast", "this", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "She scooped up your mother I think and actually helped carry her out of the house, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["She", "scooped", "up", "your", "mother", "I", "think", "and", "actually", "helped", "carry", "her", "out", "of", "the", "house", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "She did.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "The knight in naked shining armor?", "question_tokens": ["The", "knight", "in", "naked", "shining", "armor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Not a pretty sight.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "a", "pretty", "sight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "``", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "TO", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Yes, I'm not very technical, sadly, and I finished writing \"Losing My Virginity,\" the sort of second edition of it, and it was, you know, close to going to press.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "very", "technical", ",", "sadly", ",", "and", "I", "finished", "writing", "``", "Losing", "My", "Virginity", ",", "''", "the", "sort", "of", "second", "edition", "of", "it", ",", "and", "it", "was", ",", "you", "know", ",", "close", "to", "going", "to", "press", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Which camp do you think you're in?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "camp", "do", "you", "think", "you", "'re", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "It's a good question.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Do you believe more or less in god since the day after your conversation over dinner?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "more", "or", "less", "in", "god", "since", "the", "day", "after", "your", "conversation", "over", "dinner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Well, look, I believe in evolution.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "I", "believe", "in", "evolution", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["99 percent"], "LOCATION": ["Pacific"]}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Do you ever -- do you ever pray?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "--", "do", "you", "ever", "pray", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "I found myself on one of my balloon trips, where, you know, I was 99 percent definitely going to die crossing the Pacific.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "found", "myself", "on", "one", "of", "my", "balloon", "trips", ",", "where", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "was", "99", "percent", "definitely", "going", "to", "die", "crossing", "the", "Pacific", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 99, "question": "And despite the fact that you survived that, Richard, with your .1 percent, you still don't believe?", "question_tokens": ["And", "despite", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "survived", "that", ",", "Richard", ",", "with", "your", ".1", "percent", ",", "you", "still", "do", "n't", "believe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Well, look --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard"], "PERCENT": [".1 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "And what is the best, simplest way to get out of this tank?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "is", "the", "best", ",", "simplest", "way", "to", "get", "out", "of", "this", "tank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", ",", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Well, I think why it is has been well reported.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "why", "it", "is", "has", "been", "well", "reported", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Are you impressed by the way he's handled this or disappointed?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "impressed", "by", "the", "way", "he", "'s", "handled", "this", "or", "disappointed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "CC", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Look, he -- I think he would have done quite well not to have been elected when he was elected and waited four years because you know he was -- you know he had the worst stack of cards of any president for a long time.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "he", "--", "I", "think", "he", "would", "have", "done", "quite", "well", "not", "to", "have", "been", "elected", "when", "he", "was", "elected", "and", "waited", "four", "years", "because", "you", "know", "he", "was", "--", "you", "know", "he", "had", "the", "worst", "stack", "of", "cards", "of", "any", "president", "for", "a", "long", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Do you think that we need more centers like this set up by businessmen like you, encouraging that kind of entrepreneurial zeal, which many think is gone from places like America now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "we", "need", "more", "centers", "like", "this", "set", "up", "by", "businessmen", "like", "you", ",", "encouraging", "that", "kind", "of", "entrepreneurial", "zeal", ",", "which", "many", "think", "is", "gone", "from", "places", "like", "America", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "JJ", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "I think that business leaders need to play a much bigger part in tackling a whole range of issues than business leaders have done in the past.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "business", "leaders", "need", "to", "play", "a", "much", "bigger", "part", "in", "tackling", "a", "whole", "range", "of", "issues", "than", "business", "leaders", "have", "done", "in", "the", "past", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "What about Warren Buffett's idea that all very rich people like he and yourself should pay whacking more tax?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "Warren", "Buffett", "'s", "idea", "that", "all", "very", "rich", "people", "like", "he", "and", "yourself", "should", "pay", "whacking", "more", "tax", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "There is -- I think the number one priority is for, you know, government to get rid of waste of spending.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "--", "I", "think", "the", "number", "one", "priority", "is", "for", ",", "you", "know", ",", "government", "to", "get", "rid", "of", "waste", "of", "spending", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Perry"]}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "Richard, of all the runners and writers for the Republican race right now, who do you think may end up being the nomination to take on President Obama?", "question_tokens": ["Richard", ",", "of", "all", "the", "runners", "and", "writers", "for", "the", "Republican", "race", "right", "now", ",", "who", "do", "you", "think", "may", "end", "up", "being", "the", "nomination", "to", "take", "on", "President", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "Well, obviously, look, Rick Perry seems to be in the forefront at the moment.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "obviously", ",", "look", ",", "Rick", "Perry", "seems", "to", "be", "in", "the", "forefront", "at", "the", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["a month today"], "LOCATION": ["New Mexico"]}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "When do you expect to take your first spaceflight?", "question_tokens": ["When", "do", "you", "expect", "to", "take", "your", "first", "spaceflight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Well, it's very exciting at the moment and exactly a month today we unveiled the space port in New Mexico which is stunningly beautiful and right out in the middle of the desert.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "very", "exciting", "at", "the", "moment", "and", "exactly", "a", "month", "today", "we", "unveiled", "the", "space", "port", "in", "New", "Mexico", "which", "is", "stunningly", "beautiful", "and", "right", "out", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "the", "desert", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "Are you going to be the guy that makes me come closer to my children?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "be", "the", "guy", "that", "makes", "me", "come", "closer", "to", "my", "children", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "I hope so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "How many have you actually sold?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "have", "you", "actually", "sold", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "We've nearly reached 500.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "nearly", "reached", "500", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Did you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "And I asked him what he thought about your program.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "asked", "him", "what", "he", "thought", "about", "your", "program", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Did you write that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "write", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "``", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 274, "question": "A petite scene stealer?", "question_tokens": ["A", "petite", "scene", "stealer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "I wanted to hear you say \"petite scene stealer.\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wanted", "to", "hear", "you", "say", "``", "petite", "scene", "stealer", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Are you really 4 foot, 11?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "really", "4", "foot", ",", "11", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "CD", "NN", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Yeah, 90 pounds.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "90", "pounds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Do you just have a tendency to spew something out you instantly regret?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "just", "have", "a", "tendency", "to", "spew", "something", "out", "you", "instantly", "regret", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Actually, no one knows this story, but this kind of sums it up.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "no", "one", "knows", "this", "story", ",", "but", "this", "kind", "of", "sums", "it", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "My queen?", "question_tokens": ["My", "queen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Your queen.", "answer_tokens": ["Your", "queen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "You went up to a British admiral and asked him to get you a drink?", "question_tokens": ["You", "went", "up", "to", "a", "British", "admiral", "and", "asked", "him", "to", "get", "you", "a", "drink", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Not just a admiral, he was the head of the entire military.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "just", "a", "admiral", ",", "he", "was", "the", "head", "of", "the", "entire", "military", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "The chief of our armed forces?", "question_tokens": ["The", "chief", "of", "our", "armed", "forces", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "You asked him to get you a drink?", "question_tokens": ["You", "asked", "him", "to", "get", "you", "a", "drink", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "That is right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Did you meet the queen?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "meet", "the", "queen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "Of course, twice.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", ",", "twice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "What happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Well, the first night was wonderful because you address her and you only touch her if she touches you.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "first", "night", "was", "wonderful", "because", "you", "address", "her", "and", "you", "only", "touch", "her", "if", "she", "touches", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oklahoma"]}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "''", "IN", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "RB", "VBP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "What was it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "\"People Will Say We're in Love\" from \"Oklahoma,\" oddly know, which is where I'm from.", "answer_tokens": ["``", "People", "Will", "Say", "We", "'re", "in", "Love", "''", "from", "``", "Oklahoma", ",", "''", "oddly", "know", ",", "which", "is", "where", "I", "'m", "from", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 337, "question": "So you think you stumbled on a secret love song story?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "think", "you", "stumbled", "on", "a", "secret", "love", "song", "story", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "\"People Will Say We're in Love.\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "People", "Will", "Say", "We", "'re", "in", "Love", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Isn't that sweet?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "sweet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "And there was a little glimmer in her eye.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "there", "was", "a", "little", "glimmer", "in", "her", "eye", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "In what way?", "question_tokens": ["In", "what", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "HENOWETH: He's light.", "answer_tokens": ["HENOWETH", ":", "He", "'s", "light", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "You go out with her, do you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "go", "out", "with", "her", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Oprah"]}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "``", "NN", "NN", "''", "NNS", "''", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "What does she mean to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "she", "mean", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "I think for me, what -- they always talk about the \"ah ha\" moments\" with Oprah.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "for", "me", ",", "what", "--", "they", "always", "talk", "about", "the", "``", "ah", "ha", "''", "moments", "''", "with", "Oprah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Do you do that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "I certainly try.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "certainly", "try", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "How can this happen?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "this", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "Piers, help.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "help", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Anyone?", "question_tokens": ["Anyone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Trust me, there will be a big cue in here.", "answer_tokens": ["Trust", "me", ",", "there", "will", "be", "a", "big", "cue", "in", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "CC", "IN", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "I think the whole idea of having to be with someone all the time scared me, and like what would I do if I needed to be alone, go to the bathroom -- I don't know, just life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "whole", "idea", "of", "having", "to", "be", "with", "someone", "all", "the", "time", "scared", "me", ",", "and", "like", "what", "would", "I", "do", "if", "I", "needed", "to", "be", "alone", ",", "go", "to", "the", "bathroom", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "just", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Do you wish you'd married either one of those men?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "wish", "you", "'d", "married", "either", "one", "of", "those", "men", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "I think they were fabulous guys.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "were", "fabulous", "guys", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Didn't you have a little fling with George Clooney?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "n't", "you", "have", "a", "little", "fling", "with", "George", "Clooney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "In my mind.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "my", "mind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Clooney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "You did go out with Aaron Sorkin?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "go", "out", "with", "Aaron", "Sorkin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Aaron Sorkin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "I sounded kind of smart, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "sounded", "kind", "of", "smart", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "You put on your intelligent voice.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "put", "on", "your", "intelligent", "voice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Piers, you know, I'm a Christian, too.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "a", "Christian", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Do you feel disillusioned by him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "disillusioned", "by", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Well, you know, first of all, I won't say whether I vote -- who I voted for and who I will vote for because I don't think -- I'm not -- I wouldn't want to talk about that publicly.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "wo", "n't", "say", "whether", "I", "vote", "--", "who", "I", "voted", "for", "and", "who", "I", "will", "vote", "for", "because", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "--", "I", "would", "n't", "want", "to", "talk", "about", "that", "publicly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "Can you imagine that job?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "imagine", "that", "job", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "I can't think of a worse job.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "think", "of", "a", "worse", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110914pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Deal?", "question_tokens": ["Deal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "Deal.", "answer_tokens": ["Deal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]